amen the title of the message today is
the empty tomb the empty tomb Revelation
chapter 12 verse 11 the Bible says here
and they overcame him by the blood of
the Lamb and by the word of their
testimony and they loved not their lives
unto the death
they overcame him by the blood of the
Lamb and by the word of their testimony
how important do you believe a testimony
is how many of you have a testimony if
you have one let me see your hands
I think every hand should have gone up
because all of us should have a
testimony a testimony is really quite
typical a testimony is how God leads you
out of one situation and brought you
into another amen
and when we talk about our testimonies
if someone were to ask you hey what is
your testimony what what's happening is
that you're being asked how did you move
from not serving the Lord to serving the
Lord it's really a simple
is how my life was changed a testimony
is important because all of us know that
we will face obstacles in our lives and
your testimony is how you overcame that
obstacle how you overcame those
obstacles notice with me revelation 12
verse 17 because it expands upon that
thought the Bible says and the dragon
was wroth with the woman and went to
make war with the remnant of her seed
which keep the commandments of God and
have the testimony of Jesus Christ
you see it's not good enough for us just
to have a testimony the Bible says that
we have to have the testimony of Jesus
Christ now how many of you would like to
have Jesus's personal testimony we're
going to try that again because maybe
some of you didn't hear me how many of
you would like to have Jesus's personal
testimony that's who the dragon is angry
with the dragon is angry with those who
have the testimony of Jesus Christ now
if you have the testimony of Ivor Myers
what would that mean that would mean
that you were a former hip-hop artist
that would mean that you had a you know
musical contract and then somehow
another you gave that contract up to
follow Jesus Christ but you don't have
my testimony and I don't have your
testimony right my testimony is not
better than your testimony or vice versa
each one of us has our own testimony and
yet all of us must have the testimony of
Jesus Christ that means that all of us
are called to experience Jesus's
testimony and I don't know if you ever
stop to think to think about it but have
you ever considered that Jesus Christ
had a testimony
have a testimony now you think in Jesus
has a testimony like how could that be
because our testimonies are usually how
we came out of something what bad
something that we were doing wrong so
some kind of way in which we were living
wrong how we move from sin into giving
our lives to Christ that's what the
testimony that's what a test typical
testimony is but the Bible tells us here
that we must have the testimony of Jesus
Christ so you might ask what is the
testimony of Jesus Christ come again
with me to the book of Philippians
Philippians chapter 2 and we're going to
begin with verse 5 Philippians chapter 2
verse 5 the Bible says let this mind be
in you which was also in Christ Jesus
who being in the form of God thought it
not robbery to be equal with God but
made himself of no reputation and took
upon himself the form of a servant and
was made in the likeness of men and
being found in fashion as a man he
humbled himself and became obedient unto
death even the death of the cross
wherefore God has also highly exalted
him and given him a name that is above
every name that at the name of Jesus
every knee should bow of things in
heaven and things in earth and things
under the earth and that every tongue
should confess that Jesus Christ is Lord
to the glory of God the Father now let
me ask you a question how many of you
see jesus' testimony in the verses I
just read did something pretty bad
happen to Jesus what is that pretty bad
thing that happened to Jesus he was
crucified he died he faced death like
all of us must but praise God Jesus
overcame death
that's his testimony right so our
testimony is oh I overcame drinking or
all I overcame but Jesus's testimony is
I overcame death
hey Jesus tell me your story well my
story is one time I died really Jesus
yes but by the power of God I'm now
alive that's his testimony and so today
I want to actually spend a little bit of
time in his testimony because I need you
to see something very important that
that that will reveal to us what it
means to have the testimony of Jesus
Christ you see in Hebrews chapter 4
verse 14 the Bible says they're seeing
then that we have a great high priest
that is passed into the heavens Jesus
the Son of God let us hold fast our
profession for we have not a high priest
which cannot be touched with the feeling
of our infirmities but was in all points
tempted like as we are yet without what
sin let us therefore come boldly unto
the throne of grace that we may obtain
mercy and find grace to help in time of
need so now what we're being told
according to the book of Hebrews is that
Jesus was tempted just like you and I
you and I are and he was tempted in how
many points all points yet without sin
did Jesus have a testimony did Jesus
face temptation then Jesus faced hard
times and trials and tribulations yes
but he did so without sin so the
question is what does it mean for you
and I to have the testimony of Jesus and
today we are going to hear about that
testimony come with me to the book of
Matthew chapter 27 Matthew chapter 27
and as I stated earlier you know how it
is if I were to ask one of you to share
your testimony with me what would you
start out with first generally speaking
what are you going to start out with hey
tell me yours
how did you become a Christian and what
are you gonna start out with well I used
to kill people for a living
yeah something like that I don't know
it's gonna be something dramatic right
well I you go into the bad aspects of
your life that's the a part of the
testimony and then the B part is this is
how God delivered me all right so come
Matthew 27 you're saying pastor Jesus
doesn't have one of those please follow
me carefully Matthew 27 verse 1 and 2
when the morning was come all the chief
priests and elders of the people took
counsel against Jesus to put him to what
to death and when they had bound him
they led him away and delivered him to
Pontius Pilate the governor jump with me
divert by the way does this start off
pretty bad for Jesus is Jesus has Jesus
been condemned to death yeah yeah now
come with me to verse 26 we just jump in
through a couple of verses here verse 26
the Bible says then released he Barabbas
unto them and when he had scourged Jesus
he delivered him to be crucified does
that sound like something pretty bad
happening to Jesus he has been delivered
to be crucified and now check this out
verse 45 verse 45 the Bible says here
now from the sixth hour there was
darkness over all the land unto the
ninth hour and about the ninth hour
Jesus cried with a loud voice saying Eli
Eli lama sabachthani that is to say my
God my God why hast thou forsaken me
some of them that stood there when they
heard that said this man called for
Elias and straightway one of them ran
and took a sponge and filled it with
vinegar and put it on a reed and gave
him to drink the rest said let be let us
see whether he lives will come to save
him verse 50 the worst thing that can
happen to Jesus
the worst thing that can happen to
anyone
Jesus when he cried again with a loud
voice yielded up the ghost the story is
supposed to end here isn't it I mean
technically speaking this is where the
story's about that's what the disciples
thought this story ends here
all is lost can you remember a time
looking back in your life where you
probably thought
no God
it seems like the story ends here but
beloved we need to keep reading we need
to keep reading
verse 59 verse 59 the Bible
of arimathea went to Pilate and begged
the body of Jesus then Pilate commanded
the body to be delivered and when Joseph
had taken the body he what did he do he
wrapped it in a clean linen cloth and
then what did he do he laid it in his
own new tomb which he had hewn out in
the rock and he rolled a great stone to
the door of a sepulchre and departed and
there was Mary Magdalene and the other
Mary sitting over against the sepulchre
it seems like this is the end how is it
that the Bible can say that Jesus went
through everything we went through and
yet we know that Jesus never sinned well
I want you to notice a few things first
of all what is a Sepulcher what is it
it's a green but how is that grave how
did how was that grave made okay it was
hewn out of Iraq in other words the
Sepulcher was like a cave it was inside
the earth so so Jesus his body has been
laid inside the earth and then a stone
has been put over the mouth of the tomb
did he hear what I just said a stone has
been put over the what the mouth of the
tomb it's as if the earth has swallowed
up Jesus did you catch what I just said
the earth has swallowed up now do you
know what Jesus said when he was
speaking to to his people he said listen
as the son of as as Jonah was in the
belly of the fish for three days and
what three nights so the Son of man
shall
in the what heart of the earth let me
ask you did the did the fish swallow
Jonah yeah yeah so I want you to see the
comparison here that it's as if the
earth the earth swallowed up Jesus and
you can imagine that when Jonah was
swung over by the fish you can imagine
that that that it seemed like that was
it for Jonah right this is surely it he
is dead he is gone there's nothing more
that can be done the fish has just been
fed the fish is satisfied everything
good meal and just feel satisfied I want
you to imagine death the green the earth
swallowing up Jesus so where was Jesus
everyone Jesus
he was we're in the heart of the earth
he was in the heart of there he was
surrounded by the earth Jesus knows this
and carefully Jesus knows and
experienced what did what it was like to
be in the heart of the earth okay
I don't think I need to say that again
Jesus knew what it was like to be
surrounded and to be in the midst of the
earth he knew what it was like to be
caught up in the world okay
he knew what it was like to be caught
where was he he was where in the earth
in the heart of the earth in the grave
surrounded by ground surrounded by dirt
surrounded by earth beloved let me ask
you do you know what it is like to be
surrounded by the world do you know what
it's like to be caught up in worldly
things
hold on I'm a maid was Jesus caught up
in worldly things no he was not but
guess what he had an experience in which
he is in the heart of the earth and it
seems like he is surrounded
tell me the condition of the grave what
do you think it's like when that stop so
Jesus Jesus was in what darkness hmm do
you know what it's like to be in
darkness do you know what it's like to
be in darkness look at the condition of
Christ in the grave don't get me wrong
we know that Jesus was what in the grave
he was asleep in the grave but he's in
what he's in darkness he's surrounded by
watts by earth let me ask you a question
in a spiritual sense do you understand
what it means have you experienced being
surrounded by worldliness have you
experienced being caught up in darkness
yeah yeah come Jesus is in the earth the
Bible tells us in 1st John 2:15 love not
the words world neither the things that
are aware in the world If any man love
the world the love of the father is not
in him for all that is in the world the
lust of the flesh the lust of the eyes
and the pride of life is not
Crescent does Jesus know does Jesus know
that his people struggle with being
surrounded by worldliness does he
understand that it that that that
humanity struggles with being with being
caught up in darkness
Jesus was bound by what when he was
buried what did they put on him
linen cloth now do you know what the
purpose of putting linen cloth on the
dead was for you know what what they
were doing
they've been when Lazarus died what did
they do yeah he was wrapped he was bound
by grave clothes Jesus was bound by
grave clothes let me ask you what do you
think Grave coals is a symbol is a
symbol of grave clothes is a symbol of
death you put those on when you are dead
let me ask you one of the wages of sin
death let me ask you how many of you
know what it's like to be bound by grave
clothes to be bound by death you see the
Bible says the wages of sin is death and
and listen beloved the Bible tells us
that the works of the flesh the body
envy hatred and it goes down the list of
all these things let me ask you a
question how many of you remember being
bound by anger bound by fur
bound by hatred bound by Envy bound by
your desire to drink to smoke bound by
the things of this world check this out
guys I want you to look at Jesus's
condition in the grave he is surrounded
by earth he is in what darkness and he
is what he is bound you know the Bible
says that men loved darkness rather than
light light came into the world and we
have this natural thing of choosing
darkness over light we have this natural
thing of choosing the earth over
spiritual things in the Bible says this
for to be carnally minded is what's what
is carnally minded is death but to be
but to be spiritually minded is life and
peace because the carnal mind is enmity
against God it is not subject to the law
of God neither indeed can be so then
they that are in the flesh cannot please
God check this out Jesus is surrounded
in the earth he is in darkness he is
bound how many of you know what it is to
be in that condition and then the Bible
says that there was a stone over the
mouth of his tomb have you ever felt man
I just feel like there's a roadblock in
my way there is a stone in this stone is
put there to keep Jesus in
[Music]
to keep him bound to keep him in
darkness the darkness of the the the
darkness of well let me say for us why
do you think that stone is there in
front of us what do you think Satan's
trying to do with us do you think
Satan's trying to keep us in a tomb at
Gaza we want you to get this okay Jesus
was dead in the tomb we get that but
check out his condition he is surrounded
by the world by the earth he is in
darkness he is bound and there is a
stone that says you are not coming out
of here this is it for you do you
believe that Satan wants you to remain
in a condition of spiritual death that's
exactly what he wants that's exactly
what he's after
and so beloved as we look at Jesus and
as we understand the fact that he is in
this tomb he is bound he is in darkness
we begin to see that the condition of
the tomb the condition he was in in the
tomb in death is a symbol of the
condition we are in in life yeah yeah
yeah before Christ came into my life
guess what I was in darkness guess what
I was surrounded by earthly things guess
what I was bound guess what I was locked
into a tomb I want you to understand
beloved we're all born in tombs do you
catch what I just said we are all born
in tombs the wages of sin is death and
Satan's goal is to keep us locked in the
grave of unhappiness the grave of
bitterness the grave of resentment the
grave of unforgiveness you fill in the
blank
know what a seal represents right when
something is sealed it cannot be won
changed or altered Satan's goal for your
life is to keep you locked in the tomb
of anger of a resentment of bitterness
of strife of worldliness of being bound
to your old ways and let me tell you
because I think all of us can say hey we
know what it's like to feel bound and
feel like man there's no way I can ever
escape this thing that I keep doing this
sin that so easily besets me it feels
like I am locked in and then here comes
a testimony of Jesus because now as we
look at Jesus in the tomb and we realize
that the condition he was in in depth
reflects the condition we are in in life
we begin to see something amazing
because in Matthew chapter 28 verse 1
notice it with me Matthew chapter 28
verse 1 the Bible says in the end of the
Sabbath as it began to dawn toward the
first day of the week Came Mary
Magdalene and the other Mary to see the
Lord so what are they going to look for
they're not going to look for Jesus
because they know that he is in the he's
in the tomb they just want to come and
see the sepulchre this is the place
where Jesus lay the place where it
seemed you might as well have written
defeat over the stone of that tomb this
is the place where it appears that Jesus
lost that Jesus was bound that Jesus was
was surrounded by darkness and beloved
this is the place that many of us live
life so she come they come to the tomb
and then check out verse 2 and behold
hmm there was a great earthquake for the
angel of the Lord descended from heaven
and came and rolled back the stone from
the door and sat upon it someone should
say Amen his countenance was like
lightning and his raiment white as snow
and for fear of him the keepers did
shake and became as Dedmon by the way
did they set did they set jeepers up
around that to him yeah what was the
purpose of the keepers to make sure he
stayed in the tomb did you know that
every one of you have your own personal
keepers each one of us listen carefully
each one of us Satan's goal is to angels
you have this person and you and you and
you you have that person your job is to
do what keep them in the tomb keep them
from experiencing a testimony keep them
locked in their past keep them locked in
bitterness and resentment keep them
locked in the sin that does so easily
beset them keep them smoked in that
cigarette keep them drinking that up
makes your job is to make sure they
remain in the tomb and that's why I love
when I read that this angel descends
from heaven like with this faster than
has been the speed of light and it hits
the earth like what get out of here
move out of my way that Bible says the
angel rolled away the stone and sat on
it like say something say something
beloved that is the testimony of Jesus
that's what God wants to do in our lives
he's not afraid of the demons that have
us surrounded trying to keep us
depressed and trying to keep us in a
state of hopelessness he's not afraid of
that so he send this angel to wait Jesus
up in and verse 6 the Bible says of
six the Bible says here are verse 5 and
the angel answered and sentence of woman
fear not for I know whom use I know that
you seek Jesus which once was constant
was crucified yes
something bad happened to him but hold
on he is not here stop for a second I
want to stop right there she is not here
let those words be written in your mind
he is not here why for he is what He is
risen and just as evidence come see the
place where the Lord lay that is the
evidence look at the place where the
Lord lay he's not there anymore
hey you remember you remember the oil
you remember uh Timmy come look at the
place where Jimmy let look at who Timmy
used to be he's not in that place
anymore yeah back in a day I would get
angry all the time what you back in a
day I would get frustrated all the time
back in the day I would curse people out
back and I'm talking about for all of us
because we are back in the day back in
the day this is what we did but beloved
by the grace of God we become new
creatures you you can take people back
to the tomb and say yo check this out
right come here come here look that that
that was that's the place that I used to
live that's the place that that's where
I used to be this person and and I used
to do these things are used to respond
in these ways but by the grace of God we
have come out of that tomb and now are
experiencing newness of life and this is
what it means to have the testimony of
Jesus it means I once was dead dead in
what dead in sins dead in sins and trip
yes I once was there I once was bound I
once was in darkness I once was
surrounded by the earth by worldly
things but by the grace of God I am now
alive I don't believe you come come here
let me show you who I used to be let me
show you the place where I used to lay
because when people see whoa wait a
minute
that's who you used to be but that's
what you used to do I'm telling you the
greatest evidence of resurrection listen
carefully to you guys the greatest
evidence of Resurrection is an empty
tomb if there is no empty tomb people
are not gonna believe see back in the
day you know I used to act this way I
hate you
and look how and that's why I used to be
but then I became a Christian and now I
still hate you
uh I still see her in the tomb and
beloved listen to me
if Jesus's body was still in the tomb
where would Christianity be today why
don't people believe people don't
believe when we act like we're in the
tomb when people see oh we're supposed
to be godly people were supposed to be
Christians but they see us still living
and acting like we're it's still in the
tomb
what evidence what reason do they have
to believe that anything has changed
beloved it is an amazing thing to
actually be be be be be resurrected to
life be brought out of a tomb and the
greatest evidence is that the tomb is
empty and let me tell you why the tomb
was empty see have you ever eaten
something that was good when you ate it
and that's good and time went by and
maybe like an hour later you're like
stomach is feeling funny and then
another hour later you're like this is
not good right now and then and then you
begin to feel things happening in your
stomach and you begin to get that
nauseous and then before you know it you
know I hate to be expressive but because
the thing did not want settle the thing
disagreed with you right so I want you
to imagine this that fish back in Jonah
Jonah Z oh man Jonah tastes good whoo
yeah
man I've never eaten a human before this
is good stuff
humans taste so good ah and they won
they're like man this is cool man yeah
I'm gonna go tell my friends and I ate
this man what a great experience you
should he try to eat people - great
experience and then day two comes around
and it's light
looks funny what if I ate something bad
or good or something and then day three
what happened on day three that thing
inside the bellies where was this inside
the whale of the inside the belly of the
whale began to disagree with the belly
of the whale and it got to the place
where the belly of the whale could no
longer hold the thing that was in it
when death swallowed up Jesus oh this is
good
ooh this is good stuff I have swallowed
up Jesus the earth the grave death has
just had what it thinks is the best meal
ever and you understand that on v2 the
earth began to something doesn't feel
too - right here
something's disagreeing with me death
something is disagreeing with me but
listen to me death you cannot eat up
life Jesus was the life he was the light
of the world darkness you cannot contain
light and beloved on the third day the
earth realized that it could not hold in
Jesus and advised excuse the phrase but
you understand what I'm getting at he
vomited out because it could he death
could not hold Jesus down beloved this
listen why did mmm
when Jesus is in you when Christ is in
you your tomb cannot hold you the your
grave the thing you grew up in and know
so well because you live there so long
when Christ is truly dwelling in you
light and darkness cannot dwell together
your tomb must spit you out the Bible
says in John 15:18 if the world hate you
you know that it hated me before it
hated you how do we know that the world
hated Jesus because it couldn't even
hold on something disagreeing with me
in my belly and the earth spits Jesus
out because it could not contain him so
so so if you were of the world the world
would receive his own the world would be
comfortable with you in it if you are of
the world no problem the world swallows
you up the world surrounds you and
there's no problem good meal but because
you are what not of the world but I have
chosen you out of the world therefore
the world hateth you therefore the world
disagrees with you and you disagree with
the world come see the place this is
what marked that experience in Christ
where we desire that same thing let it
be that the angels let it be that heaven
can say look oh who are you looking for
oh you're looking for the old looking
for the old I for you looking for the
you looking for the old you fill in the
blank you fill in your name come show
you something come look at the plate
look at the tomb look at the grave in
which they used to be they are not here
anymore
someone new was risen there has been a
change was there a change in Jesus yeah
he went from death to life not from sin
to righteousness but from death to life
he went from being bound to being free
he went from being darkness to being in
darkness to coming out as the light that
was the change that is the testimony and
that's why they that have the testimony
of Jesus are so hated by the devil
because they are evidence of the power
of God to change lives
the Bible says Romans chapter 6 verse 4
Romans chapter 6 verse 4 therefore
if we are buried by baptism into death
or therefore we are buried with him by
baptism into death that that like as
Christ was raised up from the dead by
the glory of the Father even so we also
should walk in what newness of life
beloved listen to me how many of you
know what the testimony of Jesus is come
on now the Adventists answer you know
that one
what's the testimony of Jesus yeah the
spirit of what the spirit of prophecy so
what is the spirit of prophecy it's the
Holy Spirit how do we know it's the Holy
Spirit because Jesus said happy when he
has come he will guide you into all
truth and he will show you things to
want to come so if we have the testimony
of Jesus that means that we have the
Spirit of God in us and listen carefully
come back with me to Romans chapter
eight and need you to see this
Romans chapter eight if the Spirit of
God is in us Romans eight verse eleven
but if the spirit of him that raised up
Jesus from the dead dwell in you he that
raised up Christ from the dead shall
also quicken your mortal bodies by his
Spirit that dwelleth in you beloved if
the Spirit of Christ is in you you
cannot remain in your graves if the
Spirit of Christ is in you he has set
you free from the works of the flesh
there will be evidence in your life that
you are not the same person that you
used to be that is the greatest evidence
of Christ in the life and I need you to
get this beloved because the question is
why did Christ go into death why did he
go to the grave because that's where we
were did you catch what I just said the
reason why Jesus came to this earth and
humbled himself to death and went into
the tomb is because that's where you and
I live and in order for him to get us
out of the tomb he had to go into the
tomb himself in order for him to get us
out of the grave he had to go into the
grave himself but look the problem is
Jesus has no sin that's not the problem
actually Jesus went in without sin and
that's why he could actually redeem us
from our sins so he was tempted in all
points like we are and and he through
his death he redeemed us from the very
condition of being bound of being in
darkness of being surrounded of being
sealed as if nothing will ever change
with us and you know how people can
sometimes put that on you you'll never
change you're sealed you'll never change
they'll never let anyone tell you that
you will never change don't never let
anyone look at you as if you're the same
person that you used to be you know who
you used to be look I know who I used to
be if y'all don't believe me I will tell
you myself I am not the same person that
I used to be and I know many of you can
say that for yourselves look I am not
the same person I used to be you know
what even sometimes when we see like you
know you might see a person who they get
into a confrontation with someone and
they might do this see that face and
then they do this and you're looking
like did you see the face he made right
and you're thinking that you might not
know that that guy or maybe that girl
who they used to be they might they in
back in the day it would have been and
then right so what I'm saying is as
different people move in different
places Satan will always come and try to
tell you you haven't changed you're
still the same you
that that's what he mastered he wants
you to believe that there is no escape
from the tomb and beloved that's why the
testimony of Jesus is so important
because we see that through Christ
check this out Philippians Ephesians 2:1
and you has he quickened who were dead
in trespasses and sins where in time
past ye walked according to the course
of this world according to the Prince of
the power of the air the spirit that now
worketh in the children of disobedience
among whom also among whom also we all
had our conversation in times past in
the lusts of our flesh fulfilling the
desires of the flesh and of the mind and
we're by nature the children of Wrath
even as others but God who is rich in
mercy for his great love wherewith he
loved us even when we were dead in sins
has he done what quickened us together
with Christ by grace are you saved and
has raised us up together and made us
sit in heavenly places
beloved there's a reason our opening
scripture the scripture that was read
today was this the Spirit of the Lord is
upon me because he has anointed me to
preach the gospel to the poor you know
that whole text and you know how it ends
he has appointed me to open up or to
loose those who were in prison Jesus
came here so that he could come to our
prison house the grave and set us free
from being bound from being in darkness
from being surrounded by the world
beloved this is what it means to have
the testimony of Jesus Christ
I want to share just a few more thoughts
with you and then we'll close come with
me to John 20 verse 3 John chapter 20
verse 3 you got to see this about the
linen beloved John chapter 20 and verse
3 in John 20 verse 3 it's on the screen
so we're going to read through the verse
eight Peter therefore went forth and
that other disciple and came to the
sepulchre verse four so they ran both
together and the other disciple did
outrun Peter and came first to the
sepulchre and he stood down and looking
in saw the linen clothes lying yet he
went not in
then cometh slamming peter following him
and went into the sepulchre and see if
the linen clothes lie and the napkin
that was about his head not lying with
the linen clothes together but wrapped
together in a place by itself now other
translations are in in the other Gospels
it actually says that the linen clothes
were neatly folded have any of you ever
wondered about those linen clothes being
neatly folded like I've read that before
like ok so why does the Bible I go out
of the way to say you know and the
clothes were neatly folding hmm what are
those clothes represent they represent
death it's the clothing of death whose
clothing does who does a hood of that
clothing belong to it belongs to Satan
because Satan is the author off of death
those are his clothes God closes the
cause of righteousness amen not linen
clothes that's and he was he never
intended that to be for us so that
coding is the enemy's clothing and it
represents his power so when Jesus
resurrection the dead he's like you know
what so back in the world like you know
we would we we had a we had a phrase we
would use if we were fighting with
someone and that person lost we would
say he got folded up we say I folded him
up right just and you probably met in
when I was young used to watch cartoons
like you know when a cartoon character
got folded up it just mean like they
were so powerless they just got folded
up like a pretzel they love and listen
to me Jesus doesn't get up and just
throw the brave cold he gets he's like
by the way before I leave let me just
fold up the devil's power
let me just fold his clothes
let me just fold these clothes up and
show my power and my authority over
death
there was something else very
significant about this was that the the
napkin that was used to cover the head
it was separated from the rest of the
clothing the Bible says that right see
that the napkin was laying in a place by
itself so what does the napkin cover it
covers the head and then the the the
rest of the stuff was for the body so so
Christ takes this grave clothes which is
a symbol of Satan's power of who Satan
is and he separates the head from the
body do you remember the story of the
butler and the Baker in that story
remember that story that Joseph dreams
our Joseph explains their dreams to them
because the baker dreamed that at the
end of three days something was going to
happen and the butler dream but at the
happen and when what Joseph told the
Baker what'd he tell the butler first of
all he told the butler at the end of
three days you are going to be restored
you're going to be restored to your
former position does that sound familiar
to you guys was Jesus restored to his
former position at the end of three days
yeah yeah what about the Baker what
happened to him remember how his head
was going to be separated from at the
end of three days do you remember how in
genesis 3:15 there was a prophecy that
stated that jesus would bruise the head
of the serpent
while the serpent would only be able to
bruise his heel beloved listen to me at
the end of three days Jesus tore death
apart at the end of three days Jesus
separated the head from the body and
said this is what I do to death he fools
up those clothes and says I want you to
understand that that whenever you
remember my testimony I want that to be
your testimony
you can take those grave coals that you
used to wear that Satan told you you
will only wear these for the rest of
your life know that in me I can take
those grave clothes from you fold them
up to show you my power over whatever
that issue is you're struggling with and
I will give you my testimony might think
about that guys
Jesus says I will give you my testimony
I can't give you my testimony and you
can't give me your testimony but Jesus
can give all of us his testimony and
beloved that's what I want as you leave
this place today I want you to remember
this thought Jesus came to the tomb to
set me free from the things that bind me
from the things that appear that I feel
locked me in there's no escape there's
no hope Jesus says listen I can pull you
out of darkness I can take those grave
clothes off for you I can get you out of
the world I can get the world to no
longer like I can get you I can get you
the world to just yeah I can I can
change your life and the evidence will
be an empty tomb so here's my appeal
guys because the sad reality is that for
many of us we still live life in that
tomb we still live life in that tomb we
are still wrestling and struggling with
being the old person we were before we
even came to the Lord and maybe you just
didn't realize oh this is what the
testimony of Jesus is but today you're
learning you're learning oh wow I can
have that like I don't even like my own
testimony I just want the testimony of
Jesus and the powerful thing about this
beloved is that you don't need to be a
former hip-hop artist to have the
testimony of Jesus you don't have to be
a former drug dealer you don't have to
be a former person who killed you don't
have to be a former anything you know
people sometimes think man I don't
really have a testimony because I didn't
do anything really bad so you know what
am I going to share you
have to have you don't have to have that
kind of testimony in order to qualify
for the testimony of Jesus so my appeal
is very simple
today you're saying Lord I want your
testimony I want your testimony I want
to stop being the person that I used to
be out that that that maybe I still am
today I want to stop being that person I
want to stop being the person that is so
easily angered so easily upset so easily
going back into my old ways of my old
habits you give me the testimony of
Jesus if that's your desire I'm gonna
ask for you to stand to your feet Lord
give me the testimony of Jesus